<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-23T01:45:24.944Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Mine NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2953</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-mining"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to mine NFTs on the Ethereum blockchain with this beginner-friendly guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete NFT on Mintable]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2949</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/delete-nft-mintable"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are various reasons an NFT collector would want or need to delete an NFT. Discover our step-by-step guide on how to delete NFT on Mintable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Promote Your NFT Collections]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2941</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-promotion"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to know how to promote your NFT? Discover our tips and trick on how to promote your NFT collection in this guide]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Delete an NFT on OpenSea]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2921</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/delete-nft-opensea"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are various reasons an NFT collector would want or need to delete an NFT. Discover our guide on how to delete NFTs on OpenSea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete NFT on LooksRare]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2917</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/delete-nft-looksrare"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are various reasons an NFT collector would want or need to delete an NFT. Discover our guide on how to delete NFTs on Looksrare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Wash Trading?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2901</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/wash-trading"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about wash trading, a form of market manipulation that can be used to artificially increase the price of a cryptocurrency or NFT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Good NFT Communities]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2862</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-communities"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are ready to take a dive into the crazed and varied world of the non-fungible token, you aren’t alone. This phenomenon has taken the world by storm, offering a unique investment, collecting, and artistic option for users all over the globe. If you are just starting out in this adventure, it can be [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Blue Chip NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2772</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/blue-chip-nfts"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blue Chip is an investment term that first surfaced in the 1920s when Oliver Gingold, a stock quote clerk at Dow Jones & Company, noticed that certain high-priced stocks were trading at $200 or more per share. Poker players bet in blue, white, and red chips with the blue chips having a higher value. Blue-chip [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is LooksRare?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2776</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-looksrare"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most talked-about NFT platforms of 2022, LooksRare has been described as an early model of a community-first NFT marketplace that puts people above profit. LooksRare aims to transform the NFT market through its unique buying and selling system, which actively rewards users every time they make a transaction. The LooksRare team has [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is X2Y2?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2618</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-x2y2"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The online world of buying, selling, and trading NFTs, as well as the cryptocurrency marketplace, can be a confusing and jumbled mess of numbers, letters, unknown abbreviations, and jargon. To operate in the space, it is crucial to break down the meanings of the phrases and words used, so you can make informed decisions about [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best NFT Discord Communities to Join in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2909</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/best-nft-discord-communities"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are just starting out on your NFT venture, or you’re already an “old pro” in the industry, there are always benefits to learning from those around you. Discord is just one of many applications that can be used as an educational tool in your NFT game. From joining robust NFT communities to learning [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Delete an NFT?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2858</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/delete-nft"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-fungible tokens are not merely a string of numbers. They are backed by smart contracts, which are essentially a sort of digital self-executing contract. If you have a non-fungible token that has no market value or is otherwise useless to you, you can delete it. If you are a beginner with limited knowledge and just [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is NGMI and WAGMI?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2913</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ngmi-wagmi"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of the non-fungible token from a little-known digital item into a multi-million dollar market has created a unique community of adoptees that use social media sites and chat groups to interact and share ideas. Because of the novelty of NFTs and the exclusivity of these groups, crypto enthusiasts have developed a vast number [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 NFT Rarity Ranking Tools Whales Use to Profit]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3139</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-rarity-ranking-tool"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a wild and confusing world out there, and the introduction of the blockchain only opened an entirely new space of cryptocurrencies, NFTs, and Web 3.0. To fully understand some of the complex aspects of the industry, it is important to break down the definitions of the newly formed vocabulary. Additionally, learning the tools [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Know If NFTs Are Valuable?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3121</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-valuation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T12:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of the non-fungible token from a speculative asset class into a high-value commodity has generated widespread attention both in the press and on social media. While the growing acceptance of digital art has helped propel NFT ecosystems to new heights, there are many members of the crypto community who remain skeptical about the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap NFT – The Unification]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3469</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/uniswap-genie"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T14:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move that is sure to solidify its place as the leading decentralized exchange, Uniswap Labs has announced the acquisition of Genie, the first NFT market aggregator.  With a current market share of over 80%, this move will only serve to increase Uniswap’s dominance in the space. Founded by Hayden Adams, Uniswap has been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Floor Price NFT?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3382</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-floor-price"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent months, the term “price floor” has become increasingly common in discussions about NFTs. So what exactly is a price floor, and why is it relevant to the NFT market? In the NFT space, there are two seemingly simple propositions. One is that an NFT should be worth how much someone is willing to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>