<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-08T01:24:48.863Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Decentralized Web Hosting?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1009</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/decentralized-web-hosting"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet is a wild west of change. From new technologies to greater access for all, there is always something new and exciting in the industry. One of the few remaining spaces for true advancement and groundbreaking invention, the world wide web offers a plethora of opportunities and interests. One of the newer developing trends [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best NFT Tracking Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1277</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-tracking-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT market has been exploding since NFTs became the most exciting innovation in the crypto space in 2019. An NFT is a digital asset that can represent anything from a collectible to a tradeable asset like trading cards or generative art. NFT investors who are looking to make a profit or simply add to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the NFT market getting ready to run?  | EP #40 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3088</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep40"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, Jeremy is joined by Kevin Shannon to recap what has happened this week in the NFT market. They'll also break down whether we're on the verge of the next bull run or a sustained bear market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Alternative Cryptocurrencies To Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1001</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/alternative-cryptocurrencies"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies are currently more popular than ever and as the first cryptocurrency, Bitcoin has created a movement as the forerunner to the rest. However, there are plenty of other digital assets that have been created since the release of Bitcoin that is inching further into the curiosity of investors and becoming valuable cryptocurrency by making [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does a Peer to Peer Network Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=947</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/peer-to-peer-network"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “peer-to-peer” means one-on-one — and it’s perfectly suited to the computing world. In a peer-to-peer network, each node is both a client and a server. There is no top-down hierarchy where nodes are clients and servers; instead, each node is an autonomous agent that responds to centralized requests. The peer-to-peer network is one [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Ethereum 2.0?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=881</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-ethereum-2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Ethereum 2.0? How will it differ from the current Ethereum protocol? These are a few questions being asked as the development of Ethereum 2.0 gains momentum. and the community eagerly awaits the launch of the new and improved network. The Ethereum Foundation has been working on Ethereum 2.0 as the first upgrade to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Lessons From a Year of NFT Trading | EP #39 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2982</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep39"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On today's show, JWeb gives his list of 10 lessons that he has learned over the last year trading NFTs. He'll discuss some of his wins and losses, and how he has improved as an NFT trader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best NFT Tokens to Buy in May 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2881</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/best-nft-tokens"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T13:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of digital assets, non-fungible tokens (NFTs) are becoming increasingly popular. Unlike fungible assets which can be easily swapped or transferred, NFTs are unique and cannot be replaced. NFTs are often compared to collectibles, as they are one-of-a-kind digital assets that have no physical form. However, NFTs can be purchased and traded just [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Insurance – DeFi Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=869</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/defi-insurance"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the simplest terms, DeFi is short for Decentralized Finance. It’s a catch-all term for various financial protocols and platforms that run on Ethereum. From lending and borrowing platforms to stablecoins and tokenized BTC, there’s a wide variety of DeFi applications available today and because they’re running on Ethereum, they’re accessible to anyone with an [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heading to Goblintown with Nate Digital | EP #38 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2977</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep38"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy is joined by special guest Nate to recap the last week in the NFT market including the incredible run that Goblintown has been on as well as new projects Boki and AInightbirds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Decentralized Autonomous Organization?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=889</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/decentralized-autonomous-organizations"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T15:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are no stranger to Web3 then you are familiar with the language of acronyms. Those most commonly thrown around would be NFT (Non-Fungible Token), ETH (Ethereum), and the focus of this write-up, DAO (Decentralized autonomous organization) which are currently being incorporated into many blockchain projects within the decentralized finance (DeFi) landscape. Simply using [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Estate on Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=897</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/real-estate-on-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way we live and do business is changing faster than ever before. Blockchain has led the charge in disrupting our normal technological routines from financial services to how we distribute our food supply.  From cryptocurrencies revolutionizing payments to initial coin offerings challenging stock investing, it’s no surprise that this technology has made its way [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Our Ideal NFT Portfolios | EP #37 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2972</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep37"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan and Jeremy recap the weekend action in the NFT market, including the Goblin Town free mint, Chimpers reveal, and Rekt Guy by OSF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Most Popular NFT Games in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=914</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/popular-nft-games"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The video game industry has become increasingly popular over the last few years. It is now one of the most lucrative industries in the world and with the introduction of the blockchain, there are a lot of different ways to use it in the gaming industry expanding the hype of game features. Many companies have [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Invest in Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=850</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/how-to-invest-in-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain technology is rapidly increasing in popularity. However, many people seem to be confused about what investing in blockchain means. Is buying cryptocurrency enough? Or should we focus on direct investment in companies developing blockchain technology? Ultimately, blockchain investors fall into one of two categories; investing in crypto stocks or publicly traded companies. The market [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calm before the storm | EP #36 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2887</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep36"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, Dan and Jweb are talking about the recovering NFT market and what's ahead going into next week]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a DEX?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=926</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-dex"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T12:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wonderful and often wild world of crypto exchanges can get somewhat confusing when it comes to vocabulary. It seems the industry has opted to make up an entire vernacular all of its own, borrowing some words and phrases from the traditional investment environment, and making up new ones for the space along the way. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Mutant Ape Yacht Club]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=930</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-mutant-ape-yacht-club"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T12:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January of 2022, the Mutant Ape Yacht Club made headlines when its rare Serum #69 sold for a whopping 1,542.06 ETH ($5.8 million at the time), making it the largest sale of a Bored Ape “serum” to date.  The serum was bought by Deepak Thapliyal, CEO of the blockchain tech startup Chain, who had [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[101 Everyday Crypto Terms Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=922</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/crypto-definitions"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T13:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you been on Twitter or even a Discord or maybe amid a conversation involving crypto and found yourself confused by some of the terminology being thrown around? You’re not alone. As a noob or even a vet, navigating this space is ever-evolving and new terms pop up consistently. To make it in the world [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investing in NEO Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=918</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/investing-in-neo-cryptocurrency"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wild and ever-changing world of cryptocurrency comes with it its fair share of confusion. It isn’t always easy to keep track of the latest trends, new products, and marketplaces popping up constantly. To better understand one unique type of crypto, we will take a dive into NEO to better understand the NEO blockchain, NEO [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Thrive in a Bear Market | EP #35 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2870</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep-35"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, Dan and Jweb are talking about how to survive and thrive in a bearish market cycle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do NFT Auctions Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=910</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/how-do-nft-auctions-work"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T13:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many ways in which the NFT marketplace can conduct its business. Varying from platform to platform, the world wide web offers a space limited only by the imagination of its users. From the types of sales to the NFTs themselves, there is a creative and wonderful space on the net. But understanding how [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top Selling NFT Artists to Collect in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=905</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/top-selling-nft-artists"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wild world of NFTs is constantly changing. A volatile marketplace means prices and values are always on the move. That being said, the unique aspect of NFTs is that the “beauty” (aka selling price in this case) is in the eye of the beholder. Sometimes seemingly plain or similar art may go for millions, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market is recovering | EP #34 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2643</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep34"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, Dan and Jweb touch on the recent market developments, a bearish cycle, but also about how the market seems to be recovering now that ETH has bottomed out at around $2000, they also answer a question related to undervalued NFT projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Fiat Currency?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=893</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-fiat-currency"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1971, a financial crisis and declining gold reserves led United States President Richard Nixon to make a monumental economic decision that would forever change the international monetary system. On August 15, Nixon announced his New Economic Policy, a program that effectively ended the Bretton Woods Agreement and untethered the U.S. dollar from the gold [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Decentralized Social?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=857</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-decentralized-social"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Decentralized Social (DESO) is hitting news headlines at a rapid pace. Announcing recently the expansion to 1.5 million registered users, the new, layer-1 blockchain is said to be “built from the ground up” with a goal to “scale decentralized social applications to 1 billion users.” The numbers seem well on their way, with DESO [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Bear Market?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=885</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-a-bear-market"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lions, and tigers, and bears, oh my! When it comes to the financial markets, there are plenty of wild terms out there to understand, and we don’t just mean the animals. As with most industries, the world built around the financial institution comes with its own language. To better understand what these creatures mean in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Bull Market?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=877</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-a-bull-market"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no bull about it. The language of the financial industry can be more than a little confusing. Adding some animals into the mix doesn’t help. To better understand the marketplace overall, it is ideal to comprehend the unique vocabulary used by investors and advisors alike. Let’s dive into the strange “zoo” involved with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remaining calm in the storm | EP #33 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2637</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep33"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan and JWeb talk about the current bear cycle and the bleeding markets, but also touch on the recent Azuki news]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Web3?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=873</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-web3"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T14:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the next big thing on the horizon? Or is talk of a “web 3.0” just legend. It is coming. What it will end up becoming is anyone’s guess, but let’s break down the first, basic question about the new phenomenon: what is web3? Before Web 3.0 Web3, or Web 3.0, is what most tech [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>