<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-24T01:40:45.089Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calm before the storm | EP #36 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2887</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep36"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, Dan and Jweb are talking about the recovering NFT market and what's ahead going into next week]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a DEX?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=926</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-dex"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T12:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wonderful and often wild world of crypto exchanges can get somewhat confusing when it comes to vocabulary. It seems the industry has opted to make up an entire vernacular all of its own, borrowing some words and phrases from the traditional investment environment, and making up new ones for the space along the way. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[101 Everyday Crypto Terms Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=922</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/crypto-definitions"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T13:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you been on Twitter or even a Discord or maybe amid a conversation involving crypto and found yourself confused by some of the terminology being thrown around? You’re not alone. As a noob or even a vet, navigating this space is ever-evolving and new terms pop up consistently. To make it in the world [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investing in NEO Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=918</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/investing-in-neo-cryptocurrency"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wild and ever-changing world of cryptocurrency comes with it its fair share of confusion. It isn’t always easy to keep track of the latest trends, new products, and marketplaces popping up constantly. To better understand one unique type of crypto, we will take a dive into NEO to better understand the NEO blockchain, NEO [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Thrive in a Bear Market | EP #35 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2870</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep-35"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, Dan and Jweb are talking about how to survive and thrive in a bearish market cycle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do NFT Auctions Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=910</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/how-do-nft-auctions-work"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T13:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many ways in which the NFT marketplace can conduct its business. Varying from platform to platform, the world wide web offers a space limited only by the imagination of its users. From the types of sales to the NFTs themselves, there is a creative and wonderful space on the net. But understanding how [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top Selling NFT Artists to Collect in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=905</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/top-selling-nft-artists"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wild world of NFTs is constantly changing. A volatile marketplace means prices and values are always on the move. That being said, the unique aspect of NFTs is that the “beauty” (aka selling price in this case) is in the eye of the beholder. Sometimes seemingly plain or similar art may go for millions, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market is recovering | EP #34 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2643</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep34"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, Dan and Jweb touch on the recent market developments, a bearish cycle, but also about how the market seems to be recovering now that ETH has bottomed out at around $2000, they also answer a question related to undervalued NFT projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Fiat Currency?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=893</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-fiat-currency"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1971, a financial crisis and declining gold reserves led United States President Richard Nixon to make a monumental economic decision that would forever change the international monetary system. On August 15, Nixon announced his New Economic Policy, a program that effectively ended the Bretton Woods Agreement and untethered the U.S. dollar from the gold [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Decentralized Social?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=857</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-decentralized-social"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Decentralized Social (DESO) is hitting news headlines at a rapid pace. Announcing recently the expansion to 1.5 million registered users, the new, layer-1 blockchain is said to be “built from the ground up” with a goal to “scale decentralized social applications to 1 billion users.” The numbers seem well on their way, with DESO [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Bear Market?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=885</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-a-bear-market"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lions, and tigers, and bears, oh my! When it comes to the financial markets, there are plenty of wild terms out there to understand, and we don’t just mean the animals. As with most industries, the world built around the financial institution comes with its own language. To better understand what these creatures mean in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Bull Market?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=877</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-a-bull-market"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no bull about it. The language of the financial industry can be more than a little confusing. Adding some animals into the mix doesn’t help. To better understand the marketplace overall, it is ideal to comprehend the unique vocabulary used by investors and advisors alike. Let’s dive into the strange “zoo” involved with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remaining calm in the storm | EP #33 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2637</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep33"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan and JWeb talk about the current bear cycle and the bleeding markets, but also touch on the recent Azuki news]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Web3?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=873</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-web3"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T14:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the next big thing on the horizon? Or is talk of a “web 3.0” just legend. It is coming. What it will end up becoming is anyone’s guess, but let’s break down the first, basic question about the new phenomenon: what is web3? Before Web 3.0 Web3, or Web 3.0, is what most tech [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axie Infinity: The Ultimate Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=865</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/axie-infinity"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most popular metaverse games in existence today, Axie Infinity has been described as a “pokémon inspired universe” that has grown from a little-known blockchain platform into an international gaming phenomenon. The Covid-19 pandemic has only accelerated the game’s adoption, with the current version now a household name in the crypto community. Amazingly, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luca Netz | EP #3 | Web3 and Me 1/1s]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2629</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/luca-netz"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of Web3 and Me, Dan and Jweb interview Luca Netz to discuss everything around Pudgy Penguins, their past, and what's in store for Pudgy Penguins moving forward]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Blockchain Node?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1131</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-a-blockchain-node"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Isn’t technology a wonderful thing? There are so many complicated computations, unique languages full of fun vocabulary, and detail-oriented advances in an ever-changing landscape that even the best computer scientists can sometimes be confused. To add to the challenges, new concepts are adding to the space at a rapid pace, making it difficult to stay [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is NFT Anime?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=901</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-nft-anime"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T12:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most exciting trends in the NFT market today, anime NFTs have risen from a speculative idea in the minds of a few creators into some of the best-selling collections in the NFT community. As of this writing, the floor price for Azuki NFTs, the most successful anime collection to date, sits at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Decentralized Social Media The Future of Blockchain?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1005</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/blockchain-social-media-platforms"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are living in the age of social media where everyone is plugged in and life is lived vicariously through other people’s posted pictures, tweeted topics, and social statuses. Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, and Snapchat are famous examples of social media platforms; they’re easy to use, accessible, and free. But in addition to lots of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Hytha | EP #2 | Web3 and Me 1/1s]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1155</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/chris-hytha"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan and Jweb talk with Chris Hytha, creator of Rowhomes and Highrises to discuss his bike tour around the world, his projects, and anything else that's in the pipelines]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Generative Art?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=853</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T13:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art is a small word that covers a lot of ground. What art is is truly in the eye of the beholder, and, since it is not an objective but subjective topic, there is plenty of room for discussion across the industry. One new era in the artistic world is that of generative art. This [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoKitties – The Ultimate Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=842</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/cryptokitties"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T12:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of all the blockchain-based games that have captured the attention of the public over the years, none has done more to advance the adoption of non-fungible tokens than CryptoKitties. At the height of its fame, the game’s popularity was so widespread that it commanded over 25% of all network traffic on the Ethereum platform. Amazingly, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs Otherside preview | EP #32 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1146</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep32"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan and JWeb talk about more information being released on the Otherside by Yugalabs and speculate about the market movement surrounding the Otherside.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Crypto Commodity?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=838</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-crypto-commodity"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you become entangled in the wide world of cryptocurrency exchanges, it can be a confusing space. There are many terms from the traditional investing arena that crossover, though may have different meanings. A cryptocurrency, also abbreviated often as just “crypto” for short, is a digital asset. It can be a representation of a real-world [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build dApps: A Comprehensive Guide to Decentralized Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=833</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/building-dapps"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T12:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized applications (dApps) are the next step in blockchain technology. They are web applications that allow developers to create a full-featured app on the blockchain instead of just leveraging the functionality of smart contracts or tokens. In this post, we’ll explore how to build a dApp on the Ethereum network and what it means for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best DeFi Tools to Optimize Your Crypto Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=825</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/best-defi-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T13:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re investing in the cryptocurrency space, there’s a lot of unpredictability and uncertainty. With so many DeFi projects available, narrowing down which one is right for you may be difficult; the right tools will make your job easier. DeFi tools will help you analyze the DeFi ecosystem and find new opportunities to grow your [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Otherside Land, MNLTH and Llamaverse | EP #31 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1089</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep31"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, Dan and JWeb discuss more information dropped on Otherside Land, the reveal of the MNLTH and the second roadmap dropped by Llamaverse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WEB2 vs WEB3]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=821</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/web2-vs-web3"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology is an ever-changing world of new and exciting advancements. Even things that have long been a staple in society, like the world wide web, can adapt and update. Since its inception, the web has changed in many ways. The best part of technology is there is always room for that growth. It is the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>