<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-21T01:41:18.461Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Free NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2598</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/free-nfts"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people dream of claiming valuable rare items for free. NFTs are often traded for high prices on cryptocurrency exchanges, but is it possible to find them for free? Free NFTs do exist — some even have the potential to make their owners rich. It’s still early days in the game and most digital assets [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best NFT Analytics & Trading Tools in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1273</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/best-nft-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are a novice or just starting in the NFT space, you are privy to the unlimited potential to leverage the digital asset. It isn’t impossible to make money in the NFT world without the proper tools but it borders on insane to try. Having access to various tools and a full understanding of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are the Advantages of Using Blockchain for Identity Management?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1269</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/identity-management-using-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T13:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a buzz in the online world about the addition of the blockchain and its technologies. It only seems logical that we consider it to solve one of the biggest challenges of the space: identity management. Can identity management using blockchain help to stop fraud? What unique features does it offer? How has it [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do I Become a Blockchain Developer?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1264</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/blockchain-developers"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain technology is gaining momentum as the most promising technology with its potential to function as a secure and transparent way to share data. Built on a decentralized peer-to-peer network, blockchain offers trusted transactions without third-party verification, creating a universal level of trust between trading parties. Knowing blockchain technology is growing at a rapid speed, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Coins and The Ethereum Network]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1197</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-ether-coin"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether (ETH) is the main token of the Ethereum blockchain and the world’s second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization. Like Bitcoin, Ether can be used as a payment system to send payments directly to another person without a central authority such as a bank. Unlike Bitcoin, however, Ether coins can be used to create applications in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin vs Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1203</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/bitcoin-vs-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T12:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The massive surge in cryptocurrency adoption by the general public in recent years has led to a fierce debate as to which digital token will be the most valuable in the future. While hundreds of different coins exist today, there remain only two real contenders for the top spot in the eyes of the crypto [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Blockchain Be Used For Electronic Voting?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1135</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/decentralized-voting-system"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T13:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, elections have taken on increased significance in the eyes of voters as political parties drift farther apart. Every election seems to take on the mantra of “the most important in history,” with the public reporting higher levels of agitation and anxiety surrounding outcomes. However, despite the importance of modern elections, recent polls [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Decentralized Storage?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1127</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/decentralized-storage"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T14:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital world is a wild and wonderful space. With ever-changing technologies always updating and adding to the color palate, it can be hard to stay abreast of all the new and exciting terminology, tech, and concepts out on today’s market. To keep yourself informed of these new advancements, it is ideal to break down [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Essential Guide to dApp Development]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1017</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-dapp-development"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T12:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a couple of things everyone’s talking about — cryptocurrency and decentralized applications. Cryptocurrency, being the byproduct of blockchain, is the most popular amongst investors and those outside of the investment world. Bitcoin cryptocurrency is the first decentralized application that spearheads the entire crypto world. However, there have been other decentralized applications created since. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Decentralized Web Hosting?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1009</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/decentralized-web-hosting"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet is a wild west of change. From new technologies to greater access for all, there is always something new and exciting in the industry. One of the few remaining spaces for true advancement and groundbreaking invention, the world wide web offers a plethora of opportunities and interests. One of the newer developing trends [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best NFT Tracking Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1277</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-tracking-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT market has been exploding since NFTs became the most exciting innovation in the crypto space in 2019. An NFT is a digital asset that can represent anything from a collectible to a tradeable asset like trading cards or generative art. NFT investors who are looking to make a profit or simply add to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the NFT market getting ready to run?  | EP #40 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3088</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep40"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, Jeremy is joined by Kevin Shannon to recap what has happened this week in the NFT market. They'll also break down whether we're on the verge of the next bull run or a sustained bear market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Alternative Cryptocurrencies To Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1001</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/alternative-cryptocurrencies"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies are currently more popular than ever and as the first cryptocurrency, Bitcoin has created a movement as the forerunner to the rest. However, there are plenty of other digital assets that have been created since the release of Bitcoin that is inching further into the curiosity of investors and becoming valuable cryptocurrency by making [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does a Peer to Peer Network Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=947</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/peer-to-peer-network"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “peer-to-peer” means one-on-one — and it’s perfectly suited to the computing world. In a peer-to-peer network, each node is both a client and a server. There is no top-down hierarchy where nodes are clients and servers; instead, each node is an autonomous agent that responds to centralized requests. The peer-to-peer network is one [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Ethereum 2.0?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=881</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-ethereum-2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Ethereum 2.0? How will it differ from the current Ethereum protocol? These are a few questions being asked as the development of Ethereum 2.0 gains momentum. and the community eagerly awaits the launch of the new and improved network. The Ethereum Foundation has been working on Ethereum 2.0 as the first upgrade to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Lessons From a Year of NFT Trading | EP #39 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2982</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep39"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On today's show, JWeb gives his list of 10 lessons that he has learned over the last year trading NFTs. He'll discuss some of his wins and losses, and how he has improved as an NFT trader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best NFT Tokens to Buy in May 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2881</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/best-nft-tokens"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T13:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of digital assets, non-fungible tokens (NFTs) are becoming increasingly popular. Unlike fungible assets which can be easily swapped or transferred, NFTs are unique and cannot be replaced. NFTs are often compared to collectibles, as they are one-of-a-kind digital assets that have no physical form. However, NFTs can be purchased and traded just [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Insurance – DeFi Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=869</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/defi-insurance"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the simplest terms, DeFi is short for Decentralized Finance. It’s a catch-all term for various financial protocols and platforms that run on Ethereum. From lending and borrowing platforms to stablecoins and tokenized BTC, there’s a wide variety of DeFi applications available today and because they’re running on Ethereum, they’re accessible to anyone with an [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heading to Goblintown with Nate Digital | EP #38 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2977</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep38"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy is joined by special guest Nate to recap the last week in the NFT market including the incredible run that Goblintown has been on as well as new projects Boki and AInightbirds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Decentralized Autonomous Organization?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=889</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/decentralized-autonomous-organizations"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T15:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are no stranger to Web3 then you are familiar with the language of acronyms. Those most commonly thrown around would be NFT (Non-Fungible Token), ETH (Ethereum), and the focus of this write-up, DAO (Decentralized autonomous organization) which are currently being incorporated into many blockchain projects within the decentralized finance (DeFi) landscape. Simply using [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Estate on Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=897</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/real-estate-on-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way we live and do business is changing faster than ever before. Blockchain has led the charge in disrupting our normal technological routines from financial services to how we distribute our food supply.  From cryptocurrencies revolutionizing payments to initial coin offerings challenging stock investing, it’s no surprise that this technology has made its way [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Our Ideal NFT Portfolios | EP #37 | Web3 and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2972</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ep37"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan and Jeremy recap the weekend action in the NFT market, including the Goblin Town free mint, Chimpers reveal, and Rekt Guy by OSF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Web3 and Me</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Most Popular NFT Games in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=914</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/popular-nft-games"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The video game industry has become increasingly popular over the last few years. It is now one of the most lucrative industries in the world and with the introduction of the blockchain, there are a lot of different ways to use it in the gaming industry expanding the hype of game features. Many companies have [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Invest in Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=850</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/how-to-invest-in-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain technology is rapidly increasing in popularity. However, many people seem to be confused about what investing in blockchain means. Is buying cryptocurrency enough? Or should we focus on direct investment in companies developing blockchain technology? Ultimately, blockchain investors fall into one of two categories; investing in crypto stocks or publicly traded companies. The market [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>