<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-28T02:01:39.477Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is dApp?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=720</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-dapp"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are just getting into the world of cryptocurrency, NFTs, and online investing in this wildly volatile and unpredictable marketplace, chances are you are lost in a mess of alphabet soup. Of course, the online world loves abbreviations. Anything to save some time, right. To help you keep all of these letters and numbers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Purchase Your First NFT as a Complete Beginner?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=692</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-beginner-guide"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T02:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you want to own an NFT? But are not sure where to begin? We can walk you through a beginner’s guide on how to set up your accounts, purchase your first NFT, and set you on the way to becoming a pro in no time. First, let’s walk through the steps that are required [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Safe NFT]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=700</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/how-to-choose-a-safe-nft"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T18:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) are a new and exciting way to invest in blockchain technology. These digital assets are unique and can represent a variety of different uses. From virtual game items to real estate, the possibilities are endless. As with anything in life, though, safety is tremendously important so it is imperative you know how [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Explained – The Ultimate Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=683</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ethereum-explained"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The initial use of Ethereum was described with the goal of building decentralized applications in an effort to provide a network that could lead to attaching real-world assets to the blockchain. The idea of Ethereum came about in 2013 primarily by programmer Vitalik Buterin. In 2014, the development work began and it was officially launched [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERC 827 – The New Token Standard]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=679</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/erc-827"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T12:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum network has been around for quite some time now and with that comes the inevitable improvements to its token standards. One such improvement is ERC827 which aims at fixing what was seen as one of its biggest shortcomings – executing calls in transfers or approvals easily without any hassle whatsoever! Coins vs. Tokens [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crypto Collectibles Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=673</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/the-crypto-collectibles-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a vast and ever-changing world of cryptocurrencies, NFTs, and volatile markets, it can be tough to keep it all straight. One of the fun and exciting ventures in the marketplace is crypto collectibles. To better understand this growing phenomenon, let’s take a look at the components that make up the space, the most popular [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proxy Smart Contract – The New Frontier]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=667</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/proxy-smart-contract"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart contracts are often considered to be a more secure and permanent form of agreement. However, because their source code cannot be changed or updated without causing an issue with the blockchain itself – which would lead to potential vulnerabilities- there needs to exist some degree of mutability for bug fixations as well as new [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>