<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-17T01:52:06.232Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://floliodev.github.io/nft-resources/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is X2Y2?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2618</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/what-is-x2y2"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The online world of buying, selling, and trading NFTs, as well as the cryptocurrency marketplace, can be a confusing and jumbled mess of numbers, letters, unknown abbreviations, and jargon. To operate in the space, it is crucial to break down the meanings of the phrases and words used, so you can make informed decisions about [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best NFT Discord Communities to Join in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2909</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/best-nft-discord-communities"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are just starting out on your NFT venture, or you’re already an “old pro” in the industry, there are always benefits to learning from those around you. Discord is just one of many applications that can be used as an educational tool in your NFT game. From joining robust NFT communities to learning [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Delete an NFT?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2858</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/delete-nft"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-fungible tokens are not merely a string of numbers. They are backed by smart contracts, which are essentially a sort of digital self-executing contract. If you have a non-fungible token that has no market value or is otherwise useless to you, you can delete it. If you are a beginner with limited knowledge and just [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is NGMI and WAGMI?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2913</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/ngmi-wagmi"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of the non-fungible token from a little-known digital item into a multi-million dollar market has created a unique community of adoptees that use social media sites and chat groups to interact and share ideas. Because of the novelty of NFTs and the exclusivity of these groups, crypto enthusiasts have developed a vast number [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 NFT Rarity Ranking Tools Whales Use to Profit]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3139</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-rarity-ranking-tool"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a wild and confusing world out there, and the introduction of the blockchain only opened an entirely new space of cryptocurrencies, NFTs, and Web 3.0. To fully understand some of the complex aspects of the industry, it is important to break down the definitions of the newly formed vocabulary. Additionally, learning the tools [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Know If NFTs Are Valuable?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3121</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-valuation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T12:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of the non-fungible token from a speculative asset class into a high-value commodity has generated widespread attention both in the press and on social media. While the growing acceptance of digital art has helped propel NFT ecosystems to new heights, there are many members of the crypto community who remain skeptical about the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap NFT – The Unification]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3469</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/uniswap-genie"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T14:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move that is sure to solidify its place as the leading decentralized exchange, Uniswap Labs has announced the acquisition of Genie, the first NFT market aggregator.  With a current market share of over 80%, this move will only serve to increase Uniswap’s dominance in the space. Founded by Hayden Adams, Uniswap has been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Floor Price NFT?]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=3382</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/nft-floor-price"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent months, the term “price floor” has become increasingly common in discussions about NFTs. So what exactly is a price floor, and why is it relevant to the NFT market? In the NFT space, there are two seemingly simple propositions. One is that an NFT should be worth how much someone is willing to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord for NFT Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2905</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/discord-nft"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are just starting out in the NFT game, someone has likely recommended that you check out Discord. As one of many spaces that can be a good place to tune into for tips, upcoming releases, and even just the latest “buzz” on the industry, it is a useful tool in your NFT collectors/investors’ [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best NFT Wallets for 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2610</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/best-nft-wallet"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of non-fungible tokens is growing at an incredible rate. There are now hundreds of different NFTs available, each with its own unique characteristics. With so many options, it can be hard to know which wallet is the best for you. That’s why we’ve put together a list of the top NFT wallets of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Free NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=2598</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/free-nfts"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people dream of claiming valuable rare items for free. NFTs are often traded for high prices on cryptocurrency exchanges, but is it possible to find them for free? Free NFTs do exist — some even have the potential to make their owners rich. It’s still early days in the game and most digital assets [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best NFT Analytics & Trading Tools in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://flolio.com/resources/?p=1273</id>
        <link href="https://flolio.com/resources/best-nft-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are a novice or just starting in the NFT space, you are privy to the unlimited potential to leverage the digital asset. It isn’t impossible to make money in the NFT world without the proper tools but it borders on insane to try. Having access to various tools and a full understanding of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FLOLiO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>